该死
Shit! Shit!
我们在下行
We're going down! We're going down!
可不是呢  哈灵顿
Yeah, no shit, Harrington!
这按钮怎么不好用
Why don't these buttons work?!
按按钮
Press the button!
你以为我在干什么
What do you think I'm doing?!
快按点什么  按按钮
Come on, press something! Just press the button!
按啊
Push it!
我的腹股沟
My groin.
掉在我的腹股沟上了
It fell on my groin.
达斯汀
Dustin!
把这个搬开
Get this off of me!
我动不了
I can't move.
大家都还好吗
Is everyone okay?
是啊  我好极了
Yeah, I'm great, now that
我现在知道苏联人不会设计电梯了
I know that Russians can't design elevators!
我想我们已确定了那些按钮不好使
I think we've clearly established that those buttons don't work.
那是按钮  肯定有功能的
They're buttons. They have to do something.
是啊  如果我们有钥匙卡的话
Yeah, if we had a keycard.
-什么  -电子锁
- A what? - It's an electronic lock.
跟装卸区门一样  如果我们没有钥匙卡
Same as the loading dock door. If we don't have a keycard,
-就打不开  所以  -我们困在这里了
- it won't operate, meaning-- - We're stuck in here.
是啊
Yeah.
你们这些呆子要知道
Just so you nerds are aware,
我今晚本该去蒂娜家过夜的
I'm supposed to be spending the night at Tina's,
蒂娜总替我掩护
and Tina always covers for me.
但如果我明天不回家参加杰克叔叔的派对
But if I'm not home for Uncle Jack's party tomorrow
我妈妈发现是你们害的
and my mom finds out you three are responsible,
她会一个个地找到你们  割了你们的喉
she's gonna hunt you down, one by one, and slit your throat.
我才不在乎蒂娜
I don't care about Tina!
或杰克叔叔的派对
Or Uncle Jack's party!
你妈妈是找不到我们的
Your mom's not gonna be able to find us
因为我们要死在苏联电梯里了
if we're dead in a Russian elevator!
要不我们爬出去
What if we climbed out?
你刚刚说要爬吗
What were you saying about climbing?
看来有人在家
Looks like somebody's home.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
哪传来的
Where's that coming from?
在我们下面
It's below us.
海斯
混蛋
Hey, dipshits!
霍金斯警局  手举起来
Hawkins PD. Hands in the air.
别逼我再说一次
Don't make me say it again!
英语
English.
你们说英语吗
You speak English?
我听不懂
I can't understand you!
I can't understand you.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
听不懂
No understand!
霍普
Hopper!
翻译     草草
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     纸袋
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
别动
Don't move!
放下枪
Drop the gun.
放下
Drop it!
你听得懂吗  大块头
You understand what I'm saying, big guy?
放下武器
Drop the weapon.
否则呢
Or what?
你要开枪吗
You going to shoot?
很好
Good.
看来你听得懂
So you do understand what I'm saying, huh?
是的
And, yeah,
你不放下枪  我就给你的蠢脑袋
you don't put that thing away, I'm gonna blow some daylight
开开光
into that thick skull of yours.
不
No.
你不会的
You won't do that.
为什么
Why's that?
因为你是警察
Because you are policeman.
警察有底线
Policemen have rules.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
想试试看吗
Wanna test that theory?
我数到三
I'm gonna count to three.
一
One,
二
two,
三
three!
霍普
Hopper!
该死
Oh, shit.
跑
Go!
快跑  乔伊
Move, Joyce!
-天呐  -走  司木露[伏特加品牌]
- Oh, God. - Come on, Smirnoff.
你跟我们来
You're coming with us!
快走
Go, go, go!
Let's go! Let's go!
快走  司木露  走
Move it, Smirnoff! Move it!
跑
Run!
乔伊  开车
Joyce! Drive!
-快  乔伊  别瞎闹了  -你开玩笑吗
- Come on, Joyce! Quit screwin' around! - Are you kidding me?
-该死  -快走
- Shit! - Go!
乔伊  开车
Joyce, drive.
-我尽力了  -乔伊  快开车
- I'm trying! - Joyce, please, drive!
开车
Drive!
快带我们离开
Get us outta here!
天呐
Oh, God!
坐稳
Hang on!
还觉得是我们政府搞鬼吗
Still think it was our government?
怪奇物语  第三季 第五集
第五章 失灵者
天呐  闭嘴
God, shut up!
-喂  -乔纳森
- Hello? - Jonathan.
你知道现在几点吗
Do you realize what time it is?
听我说
Listen to me, okay?
才早上6点
It's 6:00 a.m. and, uh,
我昨晚跟费根他们玩到很晚
I had a late night with Fagin and the gang, so--
-我在德里斯科尔住的医院  -什么
- I'm at the hospital with Driscoll. - What?
急诊
她已被药物昏迷几小时了
She's been sedated for a few hours
医生们还在做测试
and the doctors are still running tests.
南茜  拜托告诉我你在开玩笑
Nancy, please tell me you're joking.
不是开玩笑  是  我知道我疯了
It's not a joke. And, yes, I know I'm insane
不理智  不现实  但别训我了
and irrational and out of touch, but can you save your lecture,
因为我现在真的不在乎
because I really don't give a shit right now. I just...
我需要你找你弟弟
I need you to put me on the phone
来听电话
with your brother.
-什么  -乔纳森
- What? - Jonathan...
求你
Please.
他都不在家
He's not even here.
他人呢
Where is he?
他安全吗
Is he safe?
他为什么会不安全
Why wouldn't he be safe?
南茜
Nancy?
他为什么会不安全
Why wouldn't he be safe?
该死
Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch!
好  磁铁
Okay, a magnet? Magnets?
-你知道磁铁吗  -磁铁
- Do you know "Magnet"? Magnet? - Magnit.
对  磁铁
Yes, magnit.
好的  磁铁
Okay, so, uh, magnit...
我冰箱上的
on my-- my fridge,
我的冰盒子上的  它们
my icebox, and then they...
掉下来了
they fell.
消磁了  不能用了  你懂吗
They demagnetized, stopped working. Uh, do you understand?
嗯
Da.
那是因为你们在弄的机器吗
Okay, so is that because of the machines that you're working on?
-机器  -对  机器
- Machina. - Machina, machina, yes.
嗯嗯  机器
Da, da, machina.
-机器  -对  机器
- Machina, machina! - Yes, machina--
嗡嗡
Vroom, vroom.
不  不是车
Oh, not-- not the car.
海斯农场的机器
The machines at Hess Farm where--
-我们绑架你的地方  -乔伊  拜托
- where we kidnapped you-- - Joyce, please!
你俩要让我头疼死了
You're givin' me a headache, both of you!
等一下  稍等
Hold on, please. One minute.
我可有进展呢
I am making progress.
-进展  -是啊
- Progress. - Yeah.
你都知道了什么
What have you learned, huh?
你知道司木露
You learned that Smirnoff over there--
-阿列克西  -司木露是苏联人
- Alexei. - Smirnoff is Russian
为星庭工作
and works for Starcourt,
这我们都知道了
two things we already knew.
以为我们知道
Thought we knew.
但现在我们能确定了  因为我证实了
But now we know-know, because I've confirmed them.
不客气哦
You're welcome.
是吗  你证实一下这玩意能不能启动吧
Yeah? Why don't you confirm whether this baby'll start, huh?
-拉着手刹  -当然了
- Keep it in park, please. - Yeah, duh!
你做点有用的事啊
You do-- do something useful.
你去做啊
You do something useful.
启动不了
It's not working.
再试试
Try it again.
该死
Shit.
停下
Stop, stop!
闭嘴  司木露
Shut up, Smirnoff!
拜托  你听到了吗
Aw, come on! D'you hear me?
我说你闭...
I said shut your damn--
该死
Shit!
天呐
Oh, Jesus.
停下
Stop.
我以为你的朋友住在伊利诺伊州呢
I thought this friend of yours lived in Illinois.
他算不上是朋友  就是个熟人
He's not really a friend. He's more like an acquaintance.
好吧
Okay, well--
跟上
Keep up, keep up, keep up.
轻点
Easy.
好  这位熟人
Okay, so this acquaintance...
-住在伊利诺伊州吧  -对
- lives in Illinois? Correct? - Yeah, yeah.
我们要走去伊利诺伊州吗
So we're walking to Illinois?
是的  我们要走去伊利诺伊州
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna walk to Illinois.
我觉得我们星期五晚上就能到
You know, I figure we'll get there by, like, Friday evening.
希望合你的日程  天呐  乔伊
I hope that works for your schedule. Jesus Christ, Joyce.
我们不会走去伊利诺伊州的  好吗
We're not walking to Illinois, okay?
那我们在干什么
Well, then what are we doing?
我不知道
I don't know, okay?
我会想出办法的
I will-- I will figure something out.
难道印第安纳州就没有会俄语的吗
Isn't there someone in Indiana who speaks Russian that--
洗耳恭听  乔伊
You know what? I'm all ears, Joyce.
你有办法吗
I'm all ears.
你说啊
I'm all ears!
好吧
I mean, fine.
就说说
Just saying.
该死
Damn it.
我找到他了
I found him.
他在哪
Where is he?
林子里
Woods.
Woods?
他跟威尔的妈妈在一起
He's with... Will's mom.
我妈妈
My-- My mom?
他们在干什么
What are they doing?
伊...诺伊
Ill... annoy.
他们要去伊拉诺伊
They're going to Ill-annoy.
迈克  吃早餐
Mike! Breakfast!
现在没空  妈妈
Not now, Mom!
伊利诺伊州吗
Illinois? Illinois, like the state?
The state of Illinois?
伊拉诺伊
Ill-annoy.
还痛吗
Does it still hurt?
只有说话的时候
Only when I talk.
那幸好你不是迈克
Well, it's a good thing you're not Mike, then.
你会一直疼的
And you'd be in constant pain.
这不对劲  霍普一整个夏天都死盯着我
Something's not right. I can't get Hopper off my back all summer,
现在他突然要跟威尔的妈妈徒步去伊利诺伊州了
now all of a sudden, he's hiking with Will's mom to Illinois?
达斯汀也不见踪影
And Dustin's MIA, too?
这不可能是巧合
I mean, this can't be a coincidence.
那又怎样
What does it matter?
重点是  他们不在
The bottom line is, they're not here.
-得靠我们了  -靠我们做什么
- It's up to us. - Up to us to do what exactly?
找到比利  阻止他
Find Billy and stop him.
好吧  这是好
Okay, yeah, that's a really nice sentiment,
但就算一一还能找到他
but even if El could find him again,
那还不一定呢  然后呢
and that's a pretty big if, then what?
我们烤焦他
We burn the shit out of him
确保他这次不逃跑
and make sure he doesn't escape this time.
-好  然后呢  -然后我们就赢了
- Okay, then what? - Then we win.
不  瞧  这就是问题所在
No, see, that's the problem.
我们赢不了
We don't. We don't win.
我们之前把吸灵魔从威尔身体里驱逐了
We got the Mind Flayer out of Will before
可他又卷土重来
and he just came right back.
我们不光要阻止比利
We don't just have to stop Billy,
我们得阻止吸灵魔
we have to stop the Mind Flayer.
-那要怎么做到  -我不知道
- How in the hell do we do that? - I don't know.
或许一一知道
Maybe El does.
她们怎么还在里面
What are they still doing in there?
我不知道
I don't know.
女孩就喜欢一起待在厕所里
Girls just like hanging out in bathrooms.
为什么
Why?
-我不知道  -她们在密谋搞我
- I mean, I don't know. - They're conspiring against me.
你现在还担心这个
That's what you're concerned about now?
不是我最担心的事
It's not my main concern.
-是次要担心  -我以为你们都结束了
- It's just a sub-concern. - I thought it was already over.
没结束  我们只是暂时分手
It's not over, okay? We're just taking a break.
她说她甩掉你了
She said she dumped your ass.
-那不像是暂时分手  -的确不是
- That doesn't sound like a break. - It wasn't!
你们知道我们还能
You guys do realize we can
听见你们说的一切吧
still hear everything you're saying, right?
说对了吧
Conspiring.
她们就是在密谋搞我
I told you, they're conspiring.
现在没空  妈妈
Not now, Mom!
迈克  开门
Mike, open the door.
红色警报  重复  红色警报
Code red, I repeat, code red.
有人收到吗
Does anyone copy?
红色警报  重复  红色警报
This is a code red, I repeat, a code red.
红色警报  重复  红色警报  有人收到吗
This is a code red, I repeat, a code red. Does anyone copy?
我们是无辜儿童  困在了星庭商场下方
We are innocent children and we are trapped under Starcourt Mall.
红军已渗透了霍金斯  如果我们被发现
The Red Army has infiltrated Hawkins, and if we are found,
会遭到折磨和杀害
they will torture and kill us.
你别一直用那个  会耗尽电池的
Gotta take it easy on that thing. Gonna drain the battery.
-商场刚开门了  -所以呢
- The mall just opened. - So?
所以可能有人在接收范围内
So someone could be in range.
怎么  你觉得商场保安皮特会用绳子降下来
What do you think, Petey the Mall Cop is gonna rappel down here
拯救我们吗
and save the day?
好吧  你跟罗宾共度了一晚
All right, why are you such a cranky pants
怎么还那么暴躁
after getting to spend the night with Robin?
老天爷
Jesus Christ.
你能不能放弃那个瘆人的幻想
Will you just give up on your creepy dream already?
我听到你俩聊了一整宿
I heard you guys talking all night.
是啊  你们俩孩子睡觉时
Yeah. We were trying to figure out a way to open up the door
我们在想办法开电梯门
while you children were sleeping.
经过8小时
After eight hours,
我们还是毫无进展
we're still exactly nowhere, which is,
这可能是我稍有些
you know, probably just a little bit of the reason
暴躁的
why I'm feeling just...
原因之一
a tad cranky.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你觉得呢  我在撒尿  别看
What does it look like I'm doing? I'm taking a leak. Look away.
别看
Look away!
你能往别的地方瞄吗
Can you redirect your stream, please?
小心点
Be careful, careful, careful!
我们都不知道里面是什么
We don't even know what that is.
是啊  它或许能派上用场
Exactly. It could be useful.
怎么用
Useful how?
我们不吃饭  也能在这里活很久
We can survive down here a long time without food,
但如果人体不摄入水分  就会死的
but if the human body doesn't get water, it will die.
真不想戳破
I hate to break it to you,
但这可不是水
but this is not water.
对  但这是液体
No, but it's a liquid,
如果要在喝那玩意
and if it comes down to me drinking that shit
和渴死间选择
or dying of thirst,
我会喝的
I drink.
有人来了
We've got company.
你闻到了吗
You smell that?
什么
What?
尿味
Piss.
我们走
Let's go.
-走走走  -我走了
- Go. Go, go, go, go, go. - I'm going!
亨德森  走走
Henderson. Go, go.
快点  史蒂夫  我们走
Come on, Steve, let's go!
老天爷
Jesus Christ.
你还想喝那个吗
You still wanna drink that?
老天爷
Holy mother of God.
好吧
Well...
希望你们身体够健壮
hope you guys are in good shape.
说你呢  烤牛肉
Looking at you, roast beef.
我们走吧
Let's go, come on.
为什么针对我
Why me?
维勒家
一模一样
It was the same thing,
跟去年威尔的状况一模一样
the exact same thing that happened to Will last year.
看啊  看看她的体温
And look at this. Look at the body temperatures.
他喜欢冷
He likes it cold.
好吧  那么这个吃化肥的疯老太婆
Okay, so this crazy old woman who was eating fertilizer--
-是德里斯科尔太太  -嗯  德里斯科尔太太
- Mrs. Driscoll. - Right, yeah, Mrs. Driscoll.
-她什么时候发作的  -昨晚
- What time was this attack? - Last night.
嗯  具体几点
Right, but what time last night?
-大概9点  -你等了一整晚才打给我
- Around 9:00. - You waited all night to call?
我在等医生做些测试
I was waiting for the doctors to run some tests.
你没在吗
You weren't there?
我现在不是来了吗
Well, I'm here now, aren't I?
哈利路亚
Hallelujah!
那么  你们的桑拿测试是几点
Um, so, wha-- what time was your... sauna test?
-大概9点  -大概9点
- Around 9:00. - Around 9:00.
那就证明了我的理论
Well, that proves it. That proves my theory.
她失灵了  跟比利一样
She's flayed, just like Billy.
-失灵  -吸灵魔  他吸走人的灵魂
- Flayed? - The Mind Flayer. He flays people.
控制他们的头脑
Takes over their mind.
这样一来  他们基本上就变成了他
Once they do that, they basically become him.
-如果有两人失灵  -那只能认定还有更多人
- If there are two flayed-- - We have to assume there are more.
海瑟
Heather.
比利对她做了什么
Billy was doing something to her.
她很怕
She was scared.
她在尖叫
She was screaming.
叫得很惨
Bad screams.
-还有叫得不惨吗  -麦克斯说
- What's a good scream? - Max said--
-那个不重要  -抱歉  我没跟上  海瑟是谁
- Doesn't matter. - I'm sorry, I'm lost. Who is Heather?
-她是泳池的救生员  -海瑟·霍利维吗
- She's a lifeguard at the pool. - Heather Holloway?
汤姆
Tom.
不是吧
Seriously?
欢迎来到我的世界
Welcome to my world.
系安全带
Seat belts.
-天呐  你能离我远点吗  -什么
- Oh, my God. Can you not walk so close? - What?
你走路时离我远点  你好臭
Can you not walk so close to me? You stink.
我懂  你在生气  是吗
I get it, I get it. You're upset, right?
因为我把车炸了
'Cause I, uh... I blew up the car?
是啊  我还在车里呢
Yeah, with me in it.
我想提醒你件事  乔伊
Well, I just want to remind you of something, Joyce.
-我可不是机械师  -显然的
- I am not a mechanic. - Yeah, clearly.
所以你该听阿列克西的
That's why you should've listened to Alexei.
是啊  你的新男友  是吧
Oh, right, yeah. Your new boyfriend, right?
是啊  今后每个跟我说话的男人肯定是我男友
Yes. Every man I talk to from now on has to be my boyfriend.
他是有点像个苏联版的斯考特·克拉克
Yeah, he reminds me a bit of a Russian Scott Clarke.
又来了
Oh, here we go.
或许你们该去约会
Maybe you should go on a date.
比如说  去恩佐餐厅
I don't know, I'm thinking, like, Enzo's?
怎么了
What?
他跑了
He's running.
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch!
司木露
Smirnoff!
给我回来
Get back here!
过来
C'mere!
Hey, c'mere!
你要付钱吗
You all gonna pay for those?
你是什么人  赏金猎人吗
So, what are you, some kinda bounty hunter?
我是警察
I'm a cop.
我在卧底
I'm undercover.
凯伦  是乔伊
Karen, it's Joyce.
是啊  我想问问威尔
Yeah, I-- I'm just checking on Will.
去看电影了
At the movies?
把你的嘴巴闭牢
Just keep your mouth shut, all right?
好  好  上车  快  上车
All right, all right, hop in. Come on, get in.
你少来
You "Hey!" You "Hey!"
这可是紧急警方事务
This is a police emergency, all right?
我需要征用你的车
I need to commandeer your vehicle.
什么
What?
只要...
As long as there's a... a...
你叫什么  先生
What is your name, sir?
-托德  -托德
- Todd. - Todd?
-对  -托德
- Yeah. - Todd.
-托德  -托德
- Todd. - Todd...
听我说
listen to me.
那个人
That man in there,
我知道他看上去不像
I know he doesn't look it,
但他是全世界最危险的人之一
but he is one of the most dangerous men in the world.
他
He's, uh...
-杀了好多孩子  -什么
- murdered many children. - What?
是啊  真正的变态  我追着他跨了两州
Yeah, he's a true psychopath. I tracked him over two state lines.
怎么回事
Hey, what's going on?
拜耶斯警探
Ah, Detective Byers.
这是托德
This is Todd.
他答应把车借给我们
He's agreed to... lend us his vehicle
好转移这位危险罪犯
to transport our dangerous criminal.
是啊  他非常危险
Oh, yes, he-- very dangerous, uh,
是个伪造犯
forger... er.
是啊  是儿童谋杀犯
Yeah. Uh, child murderer.
-什么  -我们该走了
- Child murderer? - We should really get going.
我怎么拿回我的车
Hey, how do I get my car back?
-联系警局  -哪个警局
- You just call the station. - What station?
这歌太好听了  托德
Ooh, I like the sound of that, Todd!
哪个警局
Hey, what station?
你在做好事
You're doing the right thing!
搞什么...
Hey, what the... Hey!
什么鬼
Dude!
你得承认  光是工程上的成就
I mean, you have to admit, as a feat of engineering alone,
就已经颇为惊人了
this is impressive.
你说什么呢  这根本是消防隐患
What are you talking about? It's a total fire hazard.
没有楼梯  没有出口
There's no stairs, there's no exit,
只有一台把你降到地狱半途的电梯
there's just an elevator that drops you halfway to hell.
他们是共党
They're Commies.
不给钱  工人就会偷工减料
You don't pay people, they cut corners.
要为苏联同志们说句话
To be fair to our Russian comrades,
这条隧道应该不是让你走的
I don't think this tunnel was designed for walking.
想想看  他们开发了运送那种货物的
I mean, think about it, they developed the perfect system
完美体系
for transporting that cargo.
像所有普通货物那样被送到商场
It all comes into the mall like any old delivery.
然后装载上那种卡车
And then they load it up onto those trucks
神不知鬼不觉
and nobody's the wiser.
你觉得他们建了个商场
You think they built this whole mall
就为了运输那种绿色毒液吗
so they could transport that green poison?
我非常怀疑那玩意只是毒液那么简单
I very seriously doubt it's something as boring as poison.
肯定贵重得多  像是钷什么的
It's gotta be much more valuable, like promethium or something.
钷是什么
What the hell is promethium?
维克托·斯通的爸爸
It's what Victor Stone's dad used
用它来制作半机械人的仿生和控制部件
to make Cyborg's bionic and cybernetic components.
你们都好书呆  我都不舒服了
You're all so nerdy, it makes me physically ill.
不不  别把我跟他们归在一起
No, no, no. No, don't lump me in with them.
我可不是书呆子
I'm not a nerd, all right?
干吗这么敏感  哈灵顿
Why so sensitive, Harrington?
怕在10岁孩子面前掉价吗
Afraid of losing cool points to a ten-year-old child?
不  我只是说  我完全不知道什么叫普罗米修斯
No, I'm just saying I don't know jack shit about Prometheus.
是钷
Promethium.
普罗米修斯是希腊神话里的人物
Prometheus is a Greek mythological figure,
随便了  我就是说
but whatever. All I'm saying is,
那玩意可能是用来制造什么的原料
it's probably being used to make something.
或是驱动什么
Or power something.
-就像核武吗  -对
- Like a nuclear weapon? - Totally.
走向核武  好啊
Walking towards a nuclear weapon. That's great.
-太好了  -但如果他们在建造什么
- That'd be great. - But if they're building something,
为什么选这里
why here?
偏偏要来霍金斯啊  不是吧
I mean, Hawkins. Seriously. Of all places.
我们说好了也就是去迪士尼乐园路上的休息站
At the very best, we're a toilet stop on your way to Disneyland,
但或许就是这样  或许是我们...
but maybe that's it. Maybe it's our very...
-你觉得苏联人知道了吗  -关于...
- You think the Russians know? - About--
-有可能  -那么有关吗
- They could. - So it's connected?
-或许吧  -怎么会
- Maybe. - How?
我不知道  但是
I don't know, but it's...
有可能
Possible.
抱歉  你们有什么想告诉全班同学的吗
I'm sorry, is there something you'd like to share with the class?
对讲机
Walkie.
"去中国听上去不错
"A trip to China sounds nice.
只要你轻轻走"
If you tread lightly."
是那个密语
It's the code.
-放送的信号源  -就在附近
- Wherever that broadcast is coming from-- - It's close.
我们知道那个信号...
And if there's one thing we know about that signal...
能达到地表
It can reach the surface.
我们走
Let's go.
汤姆
Tom?
海瑟
Heather?
天呐  好冷
Jesus, it's freezing.
你们闻到了吗
Do you guys smell that?
天呐
Oh, God.
又是化学品
More chemicals.
你觉得他们是在吃这玩意吗
You think they're guzzling this shit?
不然的话
Yeah, either that
他们就是疯狂清洁了一番
or they just went on a hell of a cleaning spree.
但去年  威尔可没吃化学品
But last year, Will didn't eat chemicals.
-是吧  -对
- Did you? - No.
这是新情况
This is something new.
克拉克老师  五年级  假设
Mr. Clarke, fifth grade. Posit.
把化学品混在一起能得到什么
What happens when you mix chemicals together?
创造新物质
You create a new substance.
-如果他们在制作什么东西呢  -在身体里吗
- What if they're making something? - In themselves?
拜托  喝这玩意会死人的
I mean, come on, if you drink this crap, it'll kill you.
是啊  如果你是人类
Yeah, if you're human.
血
Blood.
昨天
Yesterday,
汤姆前额帖了块胶布
Tom had a bandage on his forehead.
他被袭击了
He was attacked.
快报警
Call 91--
他们肯定是被绑了起来
They must have tied them.
然后被带去了某处
They must have taken them somewhere.
德里斯科尔太太
Mrs. Driscoll.
她一直说
She kept saying...
"我必须回去"
"I have to go back."
如果吸灵
What if the flaying,
是发生在别处的呢
it's taking place somewhere else?
肯定有个一切开始的地方  是吧
There must be a place where all this started, right?
一个源头
A source.
他不希望我看到的地方
Somewhere he didn't want me to see.
如果我们能找到  或许就能阻止他
If we can find the source, then maybe we can stop him.
至少也阻止它的传播
Or at least stop it from spreading
或是阻止它用那些化学品做不管什么事
or doing whatever the hell he's doing with those chemicals.
我们怎么找到
How do we find it?
德里斯科尔太太
Mrs. Driscoll.
如果她那么想回去  我们放她走呢
If she wants to go back so badly, why don't we let her?
这人就走过来
...this guy comes up to me,
我就在这里加油
I'm just pumping gas over here,
他...
and he-- Hey, whoa!
现在别惹我
Don't cross me right now!
今天忙吗
Busy day?
可以这么说吧
You could say that.
有个疯子偷了那人的车
Some psycho stole that dude's car.
还有什么
What else?
-什么  -他还说了什么
- What? - What else did he say?
那个疯子
This psycho?
别介意  但我已经跟警察都说过了
No offense, but I already went over all this with the cops.
我不是警察
I'm not a cop.
是啊  赫鲁晓夫
Yeah, no shit, Khrushchev.
该死
Oh, shit!
别看他们
Don't look at them.
看我
At me.
告诉我
Tell me
那个疯子怎么了
about this psycho.
走
Come on, let's go.
快点
Move it.
你不是说这人是个记者吗
I thought you said this guy was a journalist.
是啊  曾经是
Yeah, he, uh... he was.
曾经
Was?
看镜头
Look at the camera.
镜头  在你右上方
The camera, above you to the right.
上报身份
Identify yourselves.
吉姆·霍普  乔伊·拜耶斯
Jim Hopper, Joyce Byers,
司木露
Smirnoff.
-是阿列克西  -阿列克西
- Alexei. - Alexei.
姓氏
Surname.
我不知道
I don't know.
就是家族名的意思
Family name!
我知道  我不知道  好吗
Yeah, I know. I told-- I don't know, okay?
快开门
Open the damn door!
霍普
Hopper.
没事  别担心
It's all right. Don't worry.
他有点古怪  但是
He's a little bit eccentric, but...
完全无害的
he's completely harmless.
姓名
Name.
把那玩意从我面前拿开
Get that out of my face,
你个美国秃头猪
you bald American pig.
我虽然秃头
I may be bald,
但你戴着手铐呢
but you're the one in handcuffs,
苏联人渣
Soviet scum.
吉姆
Hi, Jim.
等等
Wait.
小心点
Watch it.
安静  人渣
Silence, scum.
-这得要多久  因为我  -不
- How long is this gonna take, because I-- - No.
-不  -不
- No. - No.
不  你无权向我提问
No, you do not get to question me.
你把一个国家敌人拖进了我家
You have dragged an enemy of the state into my home
就像个孩子把沾在鞋上的屎带进屋来一样不小心
as carelessly as a child drags in shit on his shoe.
我要搜他搜到满意
I will search him until I am satisfied.
吉姆  过来
Jim. C'mere.
过来一下  我跟你说句话
Just c'mere. I need to talk to you.
怎么了
Yeah, what?
-怎么了  -这不行的
- What? - This is not gonna work.
-什么意思  -他不是古怪  是疯了
- What do you mean? - He's not eccentric, he's certifiable.
-你还说别人  乔伊  -什么
- Glass houses, Joyce. - What?
-五十步笑百步  -拜托
- You know, pot calling the kettle black. - Oh, come on.
-喂  -怎么了
- Excuse me! - What?
帮个忙  小两口拌嘴去别处
Do me a favor and move your lovers' quarrel elsewhere.
-我们  -不不
- Oh, oh, this? - No, no, no.
我们不是小两口拌嘴
Not a lovers' quarrel, pal.
少来了
Spare me!
你有什么毛病
What is your problem?
请别说话了
Please, stop talking!
不  我们今天非常漫长
No! We have had a very long day.
我们被人射击  差点炸飞
We have been shot at, nearly blown up,
顶着酷热走了天知道多久
walked God knows how many miles in a hundred degree heat,
偷了辆车
stole a car,
同时还有个大块头疯子追着我们
all while being chased by this gigantic... psychopath,
就为了带他来见你
all so we could bring him to you.
因为不知怎么  你是会俄语的最近的人
Because somehow, you're the closest person who speaks Russian,
真是难以置信
which I can't believe.
但那无所谓了  因为很不幸  我们来都来了
But that doesn't matter because, unfortunately, we're here.
所以  如果你不介意
So, if you don't mind,
把那玩意放起来
put that thing away,
别犯浑了  问他  他在干什么
stop behaving like a jackass, and ask him what he's doing
害我的磁铁都从冰箱上掉下来了
that's making my magnets fall off my damn fridge!
拜托
Please.
好了  安全
Okay, clear.
安全  我们走
Clear, come on, let's go.
刚刚好悬
Okay, that was close.
-太悬了  -放松
- Too close. - Relax.
好吗  放松  没人看...
All right? Relax. Nobody saw...
该死
Shit.
天呐
Jesus!
-《红色黎明》  -我看到了
- Red Dawn. - I saw it.
-一楼  西北  -看到什么了
- First floor, northwest. - Saw what?
通讯室
The comms room.
你看到通讯室了
You saw the comms room?
没错
Correct.
-你确定吗  -确定  门就开了一下
- Are you sure? - Positive. The door was open for a second,
我看到里面有一堆灯光  机器什么的
and I saw a bunch of lights and machines and shit in there.
那有数百种可能性呢
That could be a hundred different things.
我愿冒险
I'll take those odds.
好吧
All right.
我们得快点行动  保持低调
We're gonna move fast, we're gonna stay low.
-好吗  -好
- Okay? - Okay.
快走
Move it.
走
Let's go.
快来
Come on.
轻轻走
Tread lightly!
你是谁
Who are you?
银猫  银猫
Silver cat... Silver cat.
我不懂
I don't understand.
中国
China?
哥们
Dude!
你做到了
You did it!
你打赢了
You won a fight!
天呐
Jeez...
-你在干什么  -拿钥匙卡好逃走
- What are you doing? - Getting us our ticket out of here.
你想再一路走回去吗
You want to walk all the way back?
我们可以在这里再待会儿
Well, we can hang out for a little bit,
放松  吃顿野餐什么的
relax, have a picnic maybe.
吃野餐  我们是为了无线电来的
Have a picnic? We came here for the radio.
这个计划好多了
This plan is way better.
如果我知道史蒂夫能干倒苏联人
If I knew Steve could knock out a Russian,
就会把那当成原计划了
that would've been our plan in the first place.
-但我猜...  -伙计们
- ...but I guess you're-- - Guys.
上面有东西
There's something up there.
我们走
Let's go.
我去
Holy shit.
不  那不叫刻薄
No, that is not mean.
那叫诚实
That is honest.
她不会知道的
She won't find out.
瞧  只有你
See, you're the only one
会说...喂喂  干什么呢
who gon' tell-- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Excuse me!
你们想去哪
Where do you think you're going?
我又是来见奶奶的
I was just going to visit my grandma again.
这是
And-- And this...
我的家人
this is my family.
-亲戚  -我不管他们是谁
- Extended. - I don't care who they are.
你清楚规矩  一次两人探视
You know the rules. Two visitors at a time.
-是啊  但是  -两人
- Yeah, but-- - Two!
妹子  这孩子是疯了
Girl, this child has lost her mind.
她带了一堆人进来
She brought a whole zoo in here.
知道吗
You know,
我昨天说的那些话
those things that I said yesterday, I...
我不是真心的
I didn't mean them.
-我知道  -我不觉得你跟那些混蛋一样
- I know. - I don't think you're like those assholes.
一点也不像
At all.
我从未那么想
I never have. I...
-我就是  -生气了
- I was just-- - Angry?
我还是不懂
Which I still don't get.
我完全  彻底
I mean, I was just completely, utterly,
丢人的
mortifyingly...
错了
wrong.
别被冲昏头了
Don't let that go to your head.
不会的
I won't.
我就是希望待你再不会质疑我
I just look forward to you never doubting me again.
拜托  你个破玩意
Oh, come on, you piece of shit!
谢谢
Thanks.
哥们  我觉得那就是了
Dude, I think that was it.
是什么
That was what?
橄榄枝
The olive branch.
什么
The what?
天呐
Oh, my God.
你真没救
You're hopeless.
好吧
Okay,
我去引开麦克斯
I'll distract Max,
给你个机会
get you an opening.
你去跟她谈谈  好吗
And then talk to her. All right?
她人呢
Where is she?
我不知道
I don't know.
-你确定是这个房间吗  -对
- Are you sure this is the right room? - Yeah.
她回家了
She's gone home.
我们就希望你们还会再来
We were hoping you might come back.
那是谁的血
Whose blood is that?
汤姆  不管你做了什么  那不是你
Tom, whatever you've done, it's not you.
是他在逼你
He's making you do this.
快跑
Go!
矮油
Owie.
快跑
Go, go, go!
跑
Run!
棒
Yeah!
-接到了  连续两个  -厉害  厉害
- Got it, two in a row. - That was good, that was good.
连续三个了
Best three in a row now.
你们物种喜欢MM豆吗
Does your species like M&M's?
我喜欢你的新造型  很酷
I like the new look, by the way. It's cool.
谢谢
Thanks.
跑
Run!
这边  这边
This way, this way!
南茜
Nancy!
有人吗  有人吗
Hello? Hello?!
这边
Here.
响了
It's ringing.
我才不管她的派多好吃
I don't care how good her pie is.
不  我不要她进我家
No, I don't want her in my damn house.
快接听
Come on, pick up!
南茜
Nancy?
你好
Hi there.
我来抓你了  神探南茜
I'm here for you, Nancy Drew.
不要
No!
乔纳森
Jonathan!
-你个贱人  -南茜
- You bitch. - Nancy!
跑
Run!
救命  救命
Help! Help!
救命
Help!
有人在吗
Is anyone here?!
南茜
Nancy.
Nancy!
你想去哪
Where are you going?
神探南茜  你在哪
Nancy Drew, where are you?
南茜
Nancy.
马可
Marco...
波罗
Polo!
下  地  狱  吧
Go... to... hell!